The solution of the previous quiz said that we
had to define the wide detail fragment layout in two
places. The layout-land and the layout-sw600dp folder. To avoid having
multiple copies of this file, we should use layout aliasing.
We can check the documentation for layout aliases to see
an example. Say we have a main layout file that's
for one pane UI. In the layout large and layout-sw600dp
folders, we want a multi pane layout. In case you're
wondering, layout large is for backward compatibility purposes for
large devices prior to Android 3.2, that's when the SW
qualifiers were introduced. So back to the point. To
avoid code duplication, we can define the two pane layout
in the base layout folder. Then, in the values-large
and values-sw600dp folders, we can create a reference so that
the main layout actually maps to the two pane layout.
In the Java code, you can reference it as r.layout.main,
but it's actually referencing the two pane layout.
This is what the detail fragment should look
like afterwards. And this is what the phone
landscape view looks like. If you rotate the
device, the phone portrait view should be different.
In the next coding task, we're going to make
the today list item look more like the other items in the list for the tablet.